Dave: Have you finished packing?
The taxi will be here in 15 minutes.
Becca: Er, nearly.
I can’t decide what to take.
Dave: Well hurry up.
You don’t need all that!
You’ll never close that suitcase.
And we can only take 20 kilos each.
Becca: Yes, I know.
Dave: You don’t need your trainers.
We’ll be on the beach most of the time!
Becca: What…I might go to the gym.
There’s one in the hotel.
Dave: And why are you taking a raincoat?
It’s not going to rain in Greece in June.
Becca: It might rain.
It sometimes rains in the summer.
Dave: And what’s that?
Becca: That’s my hairdryer.
Dave: But the hotel will have a hairdryer.
Becca: It might not have one.
Not all hotels have hairdryers.
And I need it.
Dave: And three pairs of jeans?
We’re only going to be there for a week.
Becca: They’re all different styles.
I’m not sure which one I’ll want to wear.
Dave: You need to take some things out.
Extra baggage costs a fortune.
It’s something like 10 pounds per kilo.
Becca: No, no, it’ll be fine, I promise.
Dave: Hurry up.
The traffic might be bad because of the rain.
Becca: OK, I’ll be ready in…five minutes.
Dave: The taxi’s here.
Becca: OK, I’m ready.
Can you take my case downstairs?
Dave: Erg, I’m sure this is more than 20 kilos.
It’s definitely heavier than my case.
Becca: I’m sure it’ll be OK…